这个退休派对真不错
It was a nice retirement party.
是啊
I guess.
不过还是挺可惜的
Still, it's a shame
罗斯曼教授是被迫退休的
Professor Rothman was forced to step down.
学校也没办法啊
What choice did the university have?
他已经精神崩溃了
He snapped.
理论物理学家不都这样吗
It happens to theoretical physicists all the time.
我想知道谢尔顿还有多久才崩溃
I wonder how long Sheldon's got.
这几个虾仁大小都一样
These shrimp are all the same size.
吃的时候都找不到一个有逻辑的次序
There's no the logical order to eat them in.
没多久了
Can't be very long.
看啊  这是罗斯曼的办公室人去楼空
Hey, look, there's Rothman's empty office.
-真可悲  -对啊  -超可悲的
- Sad. Mm, indeed. - Yeah. - So sad.
归我了
Dibs.
各位好呀
What's up, fellas?
你在这儿干嘛  克莱皮克
What are you doing here, Kripke?
量一量我的新办公室该装多大的窗帘啊
Ah, measuring my new office for drapes.
这不是你的新办公室
This is not your office.
归谁还不一定呢
It hasn't been assigned yet.
早在圣诞节派对上
Well, I called dibs at the Christmas party
罗斯曼教授试图跟玩具盒里的公仔做爱时
when Professor Rothman tried to have intercourse
我就说了这里归我了
with the Toys for Tots collection box.
归你
Dibs?!
咱这儿可是堂堂的大学  不是游乐场
This is a university, not a playground.
办公室可不会因为
Offices are not assigned
谁喊归谁就归谁
because someone called dibs.
你刚就喊了
You just called dibs.
闭嘴
Shut it.
办公室的分配得根据资历来
Offices are assigned by seniority.
我先来的学校
I arrived at the university first.
我先来的办公室
I arrived at the office first.
我就是传说中的"早起的鸟儿"
I'm the proverbial early bird.
诸位
Gentlemen.
罗斯曼教授
Professor Rothman.
晚上好
Good evening.
真好  现在又开始流行戴帽子了
I'm glad that men are wearing hats again.
真的显得很高贵
They're so distinguished.
■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧原创翻译 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：MADD  Joanna  海因里希  娜姬雅
后期：LL    时间轴：godwuwen
■
校对：YY     总监：YY
生活大爆炸  第五季第十七集
我有样小东西要送给你
I got you a little something.
小东西
A little something?
哇  这个...
Oh, it...
这也太大了吧
Oh, this is huge.
你对我的帮助才叫大呢
What's huge is what you've done for me.
别啊  艾米  我从没帮过你什么
Oh, no, Amy, I haven't done anything.
不  在认识你之前  我是一个在舞会上坐冷板凳的胆小鬼
No, no, before I met you, I was a mousy wallflower.
可你看看我现在
But look at me now.
就像那种热衷于各种派对的城市潮女
I'm like some kind of downtown hipster party girl.
有闺蜜  有男友
With a posse, a boyfriend
还有一个能镇住全场的新蕾丝文胸
and a new lace bra that hooks in the front, of all things.
快打开  快打开
Open it. Open it.
好吧
Okay.
我想送你一件前所未有的礼物
I wanted to get you something you didn't have.
哇
Wow!
我...我不知道该说...
I... I don't know what to...
哇
Wow.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
我喜不喜欢  哇
Do I like it? Wow.
那你准备挂在哪儿呢
So, uh, where are you gonna hang it?
上帝啊  还得挂起来啊  哇
Oh, my God. Hang it. Wow.
这个嘛  我还得去找个钩子
Um, you know, I'd have to go get a hook
还有钉子锤子啥的
and nails and a hammer and...
-没问题  -瞧
- No problem. - Oh, look.
你都...
You got...
你...你都准备好了  哇
You just... you got it all right there. Wow.
找到他了  在洗手间呢
I found him. He's in the bathroom.
赛博特校长
President Siebert?
就不能等等吗
Can't this wait?
-不好意思  我俩有话要说  -非得现在说吗
- I'm sorry. We just need a word. - Now?
你们知道我是老板  而且手里还握着二弟呢吧
You realize I'm your boss, and I am holding my penis?
谢尔顿  咱先出去吧
Sheldon, give the man some privacy.
真是不好意思  这家伙简直无法无天了
I'm sorry. This guy's got no respect for boundaries.
你们想干嘛
What do you want?
你能亲口告诉这个疯子
Will you tell this lunatic
罗斯曼教授的办公室就应该归我吗
that Professor Rothman's office is rightfully mine?
这种事不能找你们系主任商量吗
Can't you take this up with your department chairman?
找过了  他的助理说他在休假
We tried. His assistant said he was on sabbatical.
尽管我们清楚地听见了他办公室窗户的开关声
Although we distinctly heard his office window open and shut.
二位  我有件要紧事要办
Gentlemen, there's a task I'm trying to accomplish here,
可我现在却办不了
and I'm having trouble doing it.
天啊  赛博特校长  我不想危言耸听
Oh, my. President Siebert, I don't mean to be an alarmist,
但是排尿困难可能是
but difficulty initiating a urine stream
良性前列腺增生的症状
could be a symptom of benign prostatic hyperplasia.
如果您感兴趣
If you're interested,
我可以发给您一个YouTube视频地址
I can send you a link to a YouTube video
它会告诉您如何自己进行直肠检查
that'll show you how to perform your own rectal exam.
小贴士  记得先剪指甲哦
Uh, helpful hint-- trim your nails first.
别理他  赛博特校长
Ignore him, President Siebert.
我相信像您这样的青壮年一定有一个非常...
I'm sure a young man such as yourself has a perfectly...
健康的前列腺
healthy prostate.
他在拍您的马屁呢[字面为"给您上黄油"]
Oh, he's just trying to butter you up.
顺带告诉您
And for the record,
黄油可是直肠检查的最佳润滑剂
butter is an excellent lubricant for your rectal exam.
二位  我现在允许你俩自行解决这个问题
Gentlemen, I'm going to allow the two of you to work this out
因为  第一  你俩都是优秀的科学家
because A. you're both brilliant scientists,
第二  至于罗斯曼的办公室归谁
B. as far as who gets Rothman's office,
我他妈一点都不在乎
I couldn't give the furry crack of a rat's behind.
既然我们都来了
Well, as long as we're here,
我也放个水好了
I might as well take a leak.
克莱皮克
Kripke?
怎么了
Yes?
那是我的专用尿池
You're in my spot.
这画真大
That is big.
超大
So big.
画得好丑
And ugly.
超丑
So ugly.
我该怎么办
What am I gonna do?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不可以拿下来  艾米会伤心的
You can't take it down. You'll break her heart.
看看那张脸
Look at that face.
那张让人心烦又抓狂的大脸
That enormous, unsettling, crazy face.
你说有没有可能  我会慢慢喜欢上这幅画
Is there any chance I'll learn to love it?
看情况
That depends.
你会喜欢把你画得像个爷们的画像吗
Do you like pictures of yourself where you look like a man?
好吧  把它撤下来
Allright, it's got to go.
那你回头怎么跟艾米说
What will you tell Amy?
不如我告诉她
How about I tell her
这画没有把你画进去
the painting makes you feel jealous
让你嫉妒到抓狂
because you're not in it?
不要  万一她也送一幅给我怎么办
Nuh-uh. What if she gets me one?
我已经有张我和霍华德妈妈在威尼斯海滩
I already have a picture of me and Howard's mom
双双顶着满头小辫子的合影了
getting our hair cornrowed in Venice Beach.
我已经够遭罪了
I've suffered enough.
或者我可以先拿下来
Well, I guess I could take it down
等她过来时再挂上去  但这画好重
and put it up when she comes over, but it's kind of heavy.
可惜你不像画中的男人婆那么壮
Oh, too bad you're not as strong as the dude in the painting.
看看这个
Would you look at this?
我花了二十五块跟易趣上一个小孩
I paid $25 to some kid on eBay
买了这根手工制作的哈利・波特魔杖
for a handcrafted Harry Potter wand.
结果他给我寄来根树枝
He sent me a stick.
是他在自家后院捡的一根小树枝
He went into his backyard, he picked up a stick.
上面有编号
It's numbered.
还是限量版的呢  太棒了
Limited edition. Nice.
应该是克莱皮克
Oh, that'll be Kripke.
他来这干嘛
What's he doing here?
我们准备像绅士一样解决办公室归谁
We're going to work this office situation out like gentlemen.
要是这样还不行  我就在他的茶里下毒
And if that doesn't work, I'm going to poison his tea.
-库珀  -克莱皮克  请进
- Cooper. - Kripke. Come in.
我正在泡茶
I'm making tea.
要来一杯吗
Would you like a cup?
我像穿着连衣裙的娘儿们吗
Am I wearing a summer frock?
不  哥不喝茶
No, I don't want tea.
我们直接谈正事吧
Let's get down to brass tacks.
好吧  为了保护咱俩的友谊...
Fine. In the interest of preserving our friendship...
咱俩不是朋友
We're not friends.
这话有点伤人  不过好吧
Well, that's a little hard to hear, but all right.
众所周知  外交的本质就是妥协
As you know, the essence of diplomacy is compromise.
以该本质为指导思想
With that in mind,
我提出如下建议
I propose the following.
罗斯曼的办公室归我
I will take Rothman's office,
你一边哭去吧
and you will find a way to be okay with that.
不如这样  罗斯曼的办公室归我
How about I take Rothman's office,
而你滚一边凉快去
and you go suck a lemon?
你确定不用我给你倒杯茶吗
You sure I can't get you that cup of tea?
不如你们这样
How about you decide this
用"石头剪刀布蜥蜴史波克"来决定
with Rock-Paper-Scissors Lizard-Spock?
这他妈又是什么
What the frig is that?
"石头剪刀布蜥蜴史波克"
Rock-Paper-Scissors-Lizard-Spock
是由互联网先驱萨姆・卡斯发明的
was created by Internet pioneer Sam Kass
是对经典游戏"石头剪刀布"的改进
as an improvement on the classic game Rock-Paper-Scissors.
萨姆・卡斯万岁
All hail Sam Kass.
万岁
Hail.
怎么玩的
How does it work?
非常简单
Oh, it's very simple.
剪刀剪布  布包石头
Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock,
石头砸死蜥蜴  蜥蜴毒死史波克
rock crushes lizard, lizard poisons Spock,
史波克踩碎剪刀  剪刀斩首蜥蜴
Spock smashes scissors, scissors decapitates lizard,
蜥蜴吃掉纸[同义布]  论文[布]证明史波克不存在
lizard eats paper, paper disproves Spock,
史波克使石头蒸发
Spock vaporizes rock,
最后和以前一样  石头砸坏剪刀
and as it always has, rock crushes scissors.
抱歉  再说一遍好吗
I'm sorry. Can you repeat that?
当然
Well, of course.
剪刀剪布  布包石头
Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock,
石头砸死蜥蜴  蜥蜴毒死史波克
rock crushes lizard, lizard poisons Spock,
史波克踩碎剪刀
Spock smashes scissors,
剪刀斩首蜥蜴
scissors decapitates lizard,
蜥蜴吃掉纸[布]
lizard eats paper,
论文[布]证明史波克不存在  史波克使石头蒸发
paper disproves Spock, Spock vaporizes rock,
最后和以前一样  石头砸坏剪刀
and as it always has, rock crushes scissors.
差不多明白了  再说一遍吧
Almost got it. One more time.
没问题  剪刀剪布  布包石头  石头...
Surely. Scissors cuts paper, paper covers rock, rock...
谢尔顿  闭嘴
Sheldon, stop.
他摆明在耍你
He's screwing with you.
真的吗
Is he?
那好吧
Well, then,
看来谈判陷入僵局了
it seems we have reached an impasse.
除了跟你决斗  我别无选择了
I see no other option than to challenge you to a duel.
我本该把手套甩你脸上的
I'd smack you with a glove,
中世纪欧洲骑士挑战时把手套扔向对方
对方捡起就表示接受挑战
可上周我刚把冬天的衣物收了起来
but just last week, I packed away my winter things.
现在都21世纪了
It's the 21st century.
不能随便决斗
You can't have a duel.
等一下  霍华德
H-Hang on, Howard.
巴里  你枪法有多好
Barry, how good of a shot are you?
不是用手枪  是用脑子
Not pistols. Minds.
我们举行知识问答竞赛
A trivia contest,
你来选择知识范围好了
and you may choose the field of battle.
是选择《星际迷航》知识问答
Star Trek trivia,
还是《星际迷航:下一代》知识问答
Star Trek: Next Generation trivia,
或《星际迷航:深空九号》知识问答
Star Trek: Deep Space Nine trivia,
或《星际迷航:航海家号》知识问答
Star Trek: Voyager trivia,
或者选火车模型知识问答
or model trains.
在知识问答方面你有完全优势
You have a complete advantage in trivia.
你过目不忘
You have an eidetic memory.
再加上  我好久没看《星际迷航》了
Plus, I haven't watched Star Trek
自从发现我家附近的脱衣舞俱乐部
since I discovered the strip club near my apartment
有免费自助餐后就没看过了
has a free buffet.
要找到你俩同时擅长的事情
It's gonna be hard to find something
实在是困难啊
you're both equally good at.
那你们俩都不擅长的是什么
Is there anything you're both equally bad at?
运动
Sports.
好吧  一对一
All right, this is one-on-one.
谁先投中五个  办公室就归谁  有问题吗
First person to five wins the office. Any questions?
谢尔顿  请说
Yes, Sheldon.
五个什么
Five what?
投中五个球
Balls in the basket.
这算出界了吧
It's out, right?
暂停
Time.
空间不够了
Ran out of room.
还记得以前学校的恶霸
You know all those terrible things
是怎么欺负我们的吗
bullies used to do to us?
记得
Yeah.
我明白原因了
I get it.
喂
Hey!
他故意拿球砸我
He did that on purpose!
不  他没有
No, he didn't.
他要是故意的才砸不中你呢
Nothing that's happening here is being done on purpose.
好了  别来一对一了
Okay, uh, forget one-on-one.
这次来自由投球
Let's try a free throw contest.
谁的球先碰到篮筐  办公室就归谁
First person who makes a basket wins the office.
这样太简单了  霍夫斯塔德
Making it too easy there, Hofstadter.
鬼才信
No. No, I'm not.
原力  谢尔顿
Use the force, Sheldon.
源自《星球大战》
原力
Use the force.
我需要更多原力
I'm gonna need more force.
好了  库珀  你的玻璃心准备碎成渣渣吧
All right, Cooper, prepare to have your heart broken.
那算得分吗
Do I get points for that?
好了  已经四十五分钟了
All right, we gave it 45 minutes.
玩腻了  我们来点其他的
It's no longer funny. Let's try something else.
你有什么建议
What do you propose?
数到三
Uh, on the count of three,
你们一起用力往地上拍球
both of you bounce the balls as hard as you can.
谁的球弹得最高  办公室就归谁
The highest bounce wins the office.
你死定了  库珀
Oh, you are going down, Cooper.
别这么自信  克莱皮克
I don't think so, Kripke.
我可是拍橡皮球的高手
I've bounced many a rubber ball in my day.
好了  废话少说
All right, that's enough trash talk.
一  二  三
One, two, three.
谢尔顿的弹得更高
Sheldon was higher.
恭喜你  谢尔顿  办公室归你了
Congratulations, Sheldon. You win office.
谁才是真正的体育白痴
Who's unsatisfactory in P.E. Now?
这电影真棒
Oh, what a great movie.
真敢相信你没看过《火爆浪子》
I cannot believe you've never seen Grease.
我妈妈不让我看
My mother didn't allow me to watch it.
她担心我看了会加入黑帮
She was afraid it might encourage me to join a gang.
我得走了
I've got to go.
明天我还得早起
I've got to get up early.
我们公司在测试一种
My company's testing a new steroid
据说不会让睾丸缩水的新类固醇
that supposedly doesn't shrink testicles,
最晚上班的人要负责测量睾丸的工作
and the last one there has to do the measuring.
那我差不多也要走了
I guess I should get going, too.
晚安  画里的佩妮
Good night, painting Penny.
晚安  真的佩妮
Good night, real Penny.
晚安  真的艾米
Good night, real Amy.
你不用对画里的艾米说再见
You don't have to say good night to painting Amy,
因为她一直都在
'cause she's never leaving.
晚安  真的佩妮
Good night, real Penny.
拜
Bye.
晚安  异装癖佩妮
Good night, transvestite Penny.
好了  我要把你拿下来
Okay. Let us take you off the wall.
眼不见  心不烦
Out of sight, out of mind.
真的就好了
I wish.
我能借那部电影吗
You know, can I borrow that movie?
那些唱歌的小流氓真的让我春心荡漾
Those singing hooligans really got my motor running.
当然  你拿去看吧
Sure, sure. Enjoy.
我是说  看完了再还给我  或者...
I mean, get it back to me when you can, or...
实际上  送给你好了
you know what, actually, you keep it.
就当是我给你的礼物
It's just going to be my gift to you.
-谢谢  -拜
- Thank you. - Bye.
等等  那幅画呢
Wait... Where'd the painting go?
在那里
It's right over there.
为什么
Why?
我不知道  那画感觉很怪
I have no idea. That is weird.
-你讨厌它  -没有
- You hate it. - No.
没有没有  只是它太大了
No, no. It's just, it's a little big.
-我觉得自己好傻  -没有  你不傻
- I feel like an idiot. - No, come on, you're not an idiot.
帮我把它挂回去吧
Look, just help me put it back up.
为什么  好等我走了你再拿下来吗
Why? So you can just take it down when I leave?
-我不需要你可怜我  -艾米  别这样
- I don't need your pity. - Oh, Amy, come on...
真庆幸我没做成雕塑
I'm just glad I didn't go for the sculpture.
战利品
Ah, the spoils.
终于知道为什么胜者喜欢战利品了
I see why Victors love them.
我真为你高兴  谢尔顿
I'm happy for you, Sheldon.
同时我也承认  我会怀念和你共享一间办公室的日子
But I have to admit I'm going to miss sharing an office with you.
那是当然
Oh, of course you are.
随时欢迎你来看我
Feel free to drop by any time.
-谢谢  -记得先打电话哦
- Thank you. - Yeah. Call first.
你好
Oh. Hello.
罗斯曼教授
Professor Rothman.
这已经不是你的办公室了
This isn't your office anymore.
你退休了
You're retired.
你应该说  "我看不见你"
I think the word you're looking for is... "Invisible."
我来向你道歉
I came to say I'm sorry.
不用了
Don't bother.
-艾米  别这样  -我太受打击了
- Oh, Amy, please. - I'm so humiliated.
我坐在那里看《火爆浪子》的时候
I sat there the whole time that we were watching "Grease,"
-还以为你喜欢那幅画呢  -我知道
- thinking you liked the painting. - I know.
我从电影的开题
I was a fool from "Summer Lovin'" To the very last
傻到电影的结尾
"Rama lama lama ke ding a de dinga a dong."
你说的没错  一点没错
You're right. You're absolutely right.
我应该对你说实话
I should have been honest with you
我该跟你坦白这礼实在太重了
and told you the gift was too much.
没错  太重
Yes, too much.
因为咱俩的友谊根本不对等
Because our friendship is fundamentally asymmetrical.
显然  我喜欢你多过你喜欢我
I clearly like you more than you like me.
人与人之间的感情
I don't think you can put a number on
不能用数字来衡量
how much one person likes another.
我送了你一幅十二平方英尺的油画
I bought you a painting that's 12 square feet in area.
这就是数字
There's a number.
艾米  拜托...
Amy, come on...
你要是不喜欢用英尺作单位  我可以换成美元
If you don't like feet, you can try dollars.
这幅画花了我三千美元
The painting set me back three grand.
三千...  我的天
Three gr... Oh, my God!
艾米
Look, look, Amy,
记住  你一直都是我的朋友
all you need to know is, you are my friend
我不想失去你
and I don't want to lose you out of my life.
抱歉  现在你说话我可不敢相信
I'm sorry, I'm just having trouble believing you right now.
拿上锤子  咱们走
Grab your hammer.
没用  心已经碎成渣了
No. Damage is done.
好吧  本来我不想说的
Okay, look, I didn't want to say this,
但我把画摘下来的真正原因是...
but the real reason I took the painting down was...
伯纳黛特一看见  就嫉妒得牙痒痒
because it made Bernadette very jealous.
我的天啊
Oh, my goodness,
我怎么就没注意到呢
how could I have not seen that?
这幅画简直就是
The painting is
在不停地提醒她  咱们三人中
a constant reminder that of the three of us,
就她最逊
she is the least cool.
对  没...没错...所以...
Yeah, that's... that's what it is, so...
你真是太善良了
You have such a good heart.
是啊...我尽力而为
Yeah... I try.
走
Come on.
咱们要去哪儿
Whoa, whoa, where are we going?
去把这幅画挂回你家墙上
We're going to go put this painting back up in your apartment.
-那伯纳黛特怎么办  -管她呢
- Well, what about Bernadette? - Oh, screw her.
带她玩就算给她天大的面子了
She's just lucky we let her hang out with us.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
我在努力提升这屋的温度
I'm trying to raise the temperature in here
太凉了  我激凸得都要扎破衬衫了
before my nipples tear through my shirt.
把空调调高点不就行了
Why don't you just turn up the thermostat?
问得好
Aha! Good question.
我发现我新办公室的空调开关
It turns out the thermostat for my new office
不在这个屋  对  在隔壁屋
isn't in my new office. No. It's next door,
达文波特教授的办公室里
in Professor Davenport's office,
而她正经受着更年期一波又一波的潮热
who is currently enjoying the hot flashes associated with menopause.
这里怎么有个洞
Why is there a hole here?
我新办公室为什么会有个洞呢
Why is there a hole in my new office?
我排除到只剩2种可能性
I've narrowed it down to two possibilities:
一种可能是墙里有什么东西
"There was something in the wall
而墙外有人想得到
that someone outside the wall wanted,"
另一种更让人心烦
or the more disturbing,
就是墙里有什么东西想出来
"There was something in the wall that wanted out."
好吧  至少你终于有可以打开的窗户了
Well, at least you finally got a window that opens.
多好啊
That's nice.
是吗  请听
Is it? Listen.
怎么了  难道你不喜欢风铃吗
What, you don't like wind chimes?
不喜欢  讨厌死了  而且还有更糟的呢
No, I hate them, but it gets worse.
-听到了吧  -你是说鸟叫吗
- There it is. - The bird?
跟风铃声完全不搭
It's completely out of tune with the wind chimes.
那又如何
So?
你还没明白吗
You don't get it, do you?
窗外那是只知更鸟
That's a mockingbird.
这种鸟啼声婉转曲调多变
Mockingbirds can change their song,
也就是说它唱跑调是故意的
which means he's out of tune on purpose.
它故意气我
He's mocking me.
天啊  又来了  你们感觉到了吗
Oh dear. There it is again. Do you feel it?
渐渐感觉到你是个
The growing realization
性格古怪的王八蛋吗  我们感觉到了
that you are one wacky bastard? Yep.
才不是呢  我是说这个振动
No. The vibration.
这办公室正好在地质实验室下面
We are directly underneath the geology lab,
他们又开了那个讨厌的振动筛
and they're running their confounded sieve shakers again.
喂  你们这些石猴子
Hey, gravel monkeys,
想筛石头  直接用自己脑袋摇着筛吧
if you need to shake rocks, try jiggling your heads around!
谢尔顿  淡定
Sheldon, relax.
你让我怎么淡定
How can I relax?
我的神经系统紧绷得就像竖琴弦
My nervous system is being stretched out
被这些事不停拨弄  墙洞  小鸟
like the strings of a harp and plucked by holes and birds
风声  还有那个总亮出他下垂的蛋蛋
and wind and the low-hanging scrotum
整天阴魂不散的罗斯曼教授
of the difficult-to-evict Professor Rothman.
你要是这么不开心
If you're not happy,
干嘛不把办公室给克莱皮克
why don't you just let Kripke have the office?
难不成把革命成果拱手相让
Wait, and let him win?
你觉得我疯了吗
Do I look crazy to you?
我们楼下还要思考呢
We're trying to think down here,
你们这帮研究石头的技工
you geode-loving feldspar jockeys!
还有你...
And you...
C调  D调  E调  G调  还有A调
the notes are C, D, E, G and A.
挑一个好好唱  不然我就砍了你的树
You pick one or I am chopping down that tree!
怎么样
How's that?
右边再高点
Little higher on the right.
-行吗  -再高点
- Now? - Little more.
别动了  就这样
No. That's got it.
对  好  挺...挺好
Yeah, okay. That's, uh, that's good.
告诉你个小秘密
I'll let you in on a little secret.
一开始画的咱俩是裸体的
Originally we were painted nude.
但是我让画家填上衣服了
But I had him add clothes, 'cause I thought
我觉得没必要发掘咱们的同性恋潜质
it was an unnecessary challenge to our heterosexuality.
没错  改得好
Yeah, good call.
不过  你要是改主意了
But if you ever change your mind, all it would take
只需来点温肥皂水和几块海绵[共浴]
is some warm, soapy water and a couple of sponges.
-你是说洗掉画上的衣服吗  -当然
- You're talking about the painting, right? - Sure.
救命  来人救命啊
Help! Somebody help!
这是怎么回事
What happened?
我想看看洞里有什么  结果脑袋卡住了
I was trying to see what was in here and my head got stuck.
你为什么非要看啊
Why would you do that?
这叫对科学的探索精神
It's called scientific curiosity!
快去给我弄点黄油
Now go get butter.
挺住
Hang in there.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.